The Great Showdown! Giant VS Giant!
Turn right at the next intersection, please.
Okaaay.
Crest! Don't you think you can tell us now?
Yeah! Where are we going?
I told you, this is a mystery tour to a surprise location.
So we'll find out when we get there.
Oh well... Crest is all about the secrets, I see.
No. He is just serious, intelligent, and can keep his mouth shut.
Yeah, yeah! The opposite of someone else we know!
And who might that be?
Don't let that get to you, Jun.
And what do you mean by that, Blue Cop?!
Here we are.
Our destination was Mowtown's landfill?
I've never been here before...
Now, can you tell us why you've brought us here?
Yes. Because of this.
That thing on the map?
Correct.
What is that blinky thing?
The signal from a GPS transmitter attached to Heavy Iron.
Heavy Iron?!
Do you know what you're doing?! Heavy Iron isn't one to be messed with!
Mhm. I heard from Wild Guardy.
You knew, and you still brought us here?!
So you mean... Heavy Iron is here right now?!
Yes, over there.
Waah!
We're too close!
What if we get caught?!
Don't worry! He hasn't moved an inch since I've started tracking him.
Oh... so he can't move because of his injuries from the last battle.
So... you mean Heavy Iron is sound asleep because he's recovering?
That's correct. Metal Cardbots have a self recovering function powered by nanomachines.
But... it's not enough to just sleep it off like that.
It takes up a lot of energy even to heal a single wound.
Energy?
Metal Cardbots are like humans in that way, too. We need energy even if we're not exerting ourselves.
I wonder, what do you guys eat?
We eat all kinds of fuel! Stuff like gasoline, electricity, and methane gas.
A landfill like this is full to the brim with methane gas.
You guys really eat methane?
Sure.
It's a simple pleasure, but the taste is beyond words.
He can't do much while focusing on recovery, so now may be our best chance to seal him.
Okay, Blue Cop. We gotta seal him before he makes a move.
Roger that, Jun.
Metal Breath, pickup!
What was that?!
Is that a pirate ship?!
It couldn't be...
Black Hook!
You know him?
Yes.
He was an infamous pirate on planet Machina. Everyone knew his name.
Many Star Guardians had tried to apprehend him, but were defeated instead.
Aah! Stop it! You'll wake up Heavy Iron!
Hahaha!
So you've been hiding away in a trash heap. It suits you well, Heavy Iron.
Ah...
Where are you keeping the Star Crown? My stolen treasure!
Hmph.
It's been a while, Black Hook.
The Star Crown is safe with me.
Glad to hear it!
There's nothing a pirate likes more than to loot and plunder!
You're just a common thief!
Dealing with one was bad enough, but now there are two of them?!
Jun, what do we do?
Don't worry. This might be a good thing.
Jun's right.
Let them fight it out and seal the one who loses. All we have to do is wait.
Like fishing in troubled waters.
Everyone, run!
Jun!
And who might you be?!
I know you. You're the little runt that was controlling Blue Cop.
That kid?!
You mean this Earthling child is the master of a Star Guardian?!
Don't be ridiculous.
I-Is that...
The Metal Breath? Legendary treasure of Deus Machina?!
Hand it over!!
No way! Don't even think about it!
Blue Cop, setup!
Yaah!
Jun. Are you alright?
Thank you!
There you are, Blue Cop.
So you're the surviving Star Guardian...
Yes. Even if my home planet no longer exists,
the will of Deus Machina is engraved in my memory circuit.
What a joke!
Black Hook. Let's settle our score some other time.
You're calling a truce, huh?
Guys, get out of here!
Come on, let's go!
I'll take you up on that offer, however...
The legendary treasure is all mine!!
He can't fight them both!
Jun! I'm okay!
Blue Cop, cause a distraction! Hurry!
Got it!
You slippery little pest.
Jun!
I'll be alright. You guys get outta here!
Don't overdo it!
I'll admit you got some guts, small fry!
Now, hand over the Metal Breath!
And what if I don't?!
Shadow X, setup!
Yeah! Haha!
Shadow X, launch your Spinning Cutter from the air!
Spinning Cutter!
That hurt!
Huh?
Heli-Tornado!
Huh? Where did that small fry go?!
Ahoy matey! Where ya lookin'?!
You annoying little fruit fly!
Just keep it up a little longer, Shadow X!
Leave it to me! Over here, ye salty dog!
Blue Cop, we'll be there shortly.
We have to seal Heavy Iron as soon as possible!
Roger that!
Enough with this game of tag!
Blue Cop!
Not so tough now, are you?
Wild Guardy, we need to hurry!
Got it!
Now it's time to end you once and for all!
Metal Breath, pickup!
Wild Guardy, setup!
I'll be your opponent!
You again?
I'll pay you back for this wound a hundredfold!
Not interested!
Start playing fair and show yourself!
A pirate wants to play fair? Don't make me laugh!
There you are!
Where did you run off to, Earthling child?!
Where is the pirate going now?
Uncle Edo! We need to go after him!
Oh- uh, alright! Everyone, hold on tight!
Keep it up! Wild Slash!
Wild...
Slash!
I'd like to keep playing, but let's end this now.
I still need to get some rest.
Hurry up and get out of there!
He's not gonna try that...
Hey, Heavy Iron!
If you fire that, you'll also blow the Metal Breath to smithereens!
That's none of my concern.
You piece of...
That wasn't part of the deal!
I never made a deal with you!
Captain's Cannon!
Iron Cannon!
Over there!
Could they be...
Jun...
Wild Guardy!
Jun is okay.
I thought I was done for this time...
That brought back some bad memories...
What a relief.
Do you think either one of them is down?
I don't think so.
Ugh... I can't believe this...
I only came for my Star Crown, but found myself in this mess!
Earthling child! That will be all for today.
I'll be back for your Metal Breath soon,
so take good care of it until I return!
Hahaha!
Jun, what about Heavy Iron?
I don't think that was enough to finish him off.
There's no use in sticking around. Let's get out of here!
Aah!
Hey, be gentle with that!
Ugh. Stop complaining.
Wild Guardy is fine.
Just a little tear in the fuel hose. I replaced it.
That's good to hear.
Those two were really scary.
Heavy Iron and Black Hook. Two really strong Cardbots showed up at once!
If we're going to want to seal them, we'll have to get stronger too.
Yes, Jun!
I'll leave it to you guys from now on.
What do you mean, Crest?
The thing is, I realize how foolish I've been.
In the future, I'll try to help you in different ways.
Crest!
Please take care of Wild Guardy, Jun.
Of course!